Thomas Clarke For full contact details please see my LinkedIn page or email me

Profile:

A degree in Computer Science is allowing me to explore my interests and fuel my passion for technology, from the theory of data structures to the workings of robots. I am task focused, have a positive attitude and an industrious work ethic, all of which are important for my degree and for the real world of work. I have had worked in several different working environments doing difference jobs, all of which are giving me new experiences to help build myself and prepare me for my future career. I can adapt to new environments quickly and deal with problems effectively, skills which I can apply in the technological world.

Qualifications:

Currently studying: University of Birmingham - BSc in Computer Science with a Year in Industry - September 2014 to July 2018

• 1st Year Results: Year average was 85%, with my top 3 scores being 88% (Information and the Web), 95% (Software Workshop) and 100% (Robot Programming)

John Cleveland College - September 2010 to August 2014

- A Levels: Mathematics (A*), Physics (A), ICT (A), AS History (C); Extended Project Qualification (A).
- GCSEs: 3 A*s, 6 As, 1 B and OCR Level 2 National Double Award in ICT (Distinction).

Work History:

- Software Developer, Majestic, July 2015 to September 2015: Using various web technologies and utilising D3.js, me and a team of 2 other developers are using the Majestic API to create data visualisations. The work can be seen at https://labs.majestic.com. I also represented Majestic at Leeds Hack 2015.
- Supervisor, Spar, March 2015 to present: Responsibilities include supervising sales assistants, opening and setting up the shop, handling money, maintaining some important systems and more of the shop in general and handling more customer queries.
- Sales Assistant, Spar (before promotion to supervisor listed above), October 2014 to March 2015: My responsibilities were serving customers, operating the tills and maintaining the shop interior.
- Software Tester, Crane Electronics Ltd., Summer 2014: Responsibilities involved exploring and testing a range of products to identify faults or problems and reporting them to the software engineer for revision. The main project was black box testing on an Android based device.
- Garden Centre Assistant, Woodlands Nursery & Garden Centre, October 2013 to January 2014: Responsibilities involved fast-paced customer service and till working.
- IT Department, Aston Martin, Warwick, July 2011: Responsibilities involved building new computers for the assembly line and installing them across the factory.

Achievements, Interests and Hobbies:

- Knowledge of how to program in Java, OCaml and web technologies (HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, D3.js, PHP).
- Attending various hackathons:
 - I represented Majestic at Leeds Hack 2015 (leedshack.org) as a sponsor, where I introduced Majestic to the attendees, was on hand to set hackers up with Majestic accounts, act as technical support and have discussions with them about what they

Thomas Clarke

For full contact details please see my LinkedIn page or email me

could do as projects, and was responsible for selecting winner for our prizes and awarding them.

- BrumHack 2.0 where our team created a fast-paced fighting game in Unity using C# and having to create extra C# programs to run within the game to gather information about various websites using Majestic's API.
- Programming robots using LeJOS and scoring 100% in this robotics module.
- Some experience in Android Application Development, jQuery and Visual Basic.
- I have participated in extra circular activities including:
 - o an EPQ (Extended Project Qualification) based on creating an Android Application,
 - o a Silver Crest Award based on Astronomy,
 - o a v50 volunteering award,
- Member of the Computer Science Society and Games Development Society.
- Bass guitar (achieved Merit at Grade 3).
- Socialising, live music, game design and travelling.

Other Information:

- Email: tomclarke96@hotmail.co.uk
- LinkedIn profile: linkedin.com/in/tombclarke
- Website: tombclarke.co.uk
- Full, clean UK Driving Licence, with own car.
- D.O.B.: 04/03/199
- Non smoker

Reference:

- Majestic-12 Ltd:
 - o Steve Pitchford
 - o Email: stevep@majesticseo.com
- Spar, Guild of Students, University of Birmingham:
 - o Callum Cue
- Crane-Electronics Ltd:
 - Neil McDonald
 - o Email: nmcdonald@crane-electronics.com